Charlene Drew Jarvis 131
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
- Series 1
  - "Mayoral Race/ Black Women" Eyewitness News Video Tape, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis for Mayor Video Tape, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Installation Ceremony Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Jarvis for Chair 3x30 PSA's Video Tape, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 15th Annual District of Columbia Association for Retarded Citizens Conference Video Tape, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Jarvis Speech at Democratic National Convention Video Tape, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Convention 1992 - Eleanor Holmes Newton Support Group Video Tape (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jarvis Nightline Video Tape, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Council Salaries Video Tape, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Woldnet - K. Herber - C. Jarvis Video Tape, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Decision '92 Clinton Yes Video Tape, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - B/H Smith Housing Video Tape, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Selected Television Clips from the Lincoln Theatre Grand Reopening Video Tape, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Banking Jarvis Video Tape, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - WHAT-TV/ PBS "Here and Now" Video Tape, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - ABC "Turning Point:" The Littlest Heroes- Children with Leukemia - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Worldnet - Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Platform Video Tape, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Whitman Walker Clinic Video Tape, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Friday 4/7/00 EduLibRec Hearing Budget Fall 2001 Video Tape (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Video Tape, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis in Appreciation for Devoted Service to the Shepard School Family Award, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Barney Emblem Award for Councilmember Charlene Drew-Jarvis for Generous Support of Services to Youth, Adults and Senior Citizens, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Councilmember Charlene Drew Jarvis in Appreciation for Your Support from Caribbean Business Persons of Ward 4 Award, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis Barry Farm "Delivering on a Commitment" Award, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Presented to Charlene Drew Jarvis Thanks for your Support on our Behalf and the Behalf of all Minority Enterprises in Washington D.C. Award, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - In Recognition and Appreciation to Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis Ward Four for Services and Commitment to Advisory Neighborhood Commission 4D Community Award, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - On the Occasion of the 20th Anniversary of the Peoples Involvement Corporation Presented to Charlene Drew Jarvis in Recognition of Her Outstanding Leadership and Support Award, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Award for Distinguished Service to Charlene Drew Jarvis for Devoted Volunteer Participation in the Cause of Cancer Control by a Government Employee in Washington D.C., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Presented to the Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis by the Marshall Heights Community Development Organization Board of Directors In Recognition of Your Leadership in the Economic Revitalization of Ward 7 Award, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis Council Member Ward 4 With Great Appreciation for Outstanding Leadership from Constituents of ANC-4D Single Member Districts 4D01 and 4D03 We Applaud You Award, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Florida AandM University Presented to Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis in Appreciation for the Spring 1991 Commencement Address. Thanks for Your Thought Provoking Comments and for Your Commitment to Humanity Award (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Appreciation Award: The Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis - The District of Columbia School Counselor Association Award, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - National Black Caucus of State Legislators 1994 Membership Dues Paid (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Chancellor Williams Award: Charlene Drew Jarvis - For Your Outstanding Achievements and Services to Humanity Award, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of Appreciation Presented to Charlene Drew Jarvis for Outstanding and Dedicated Service Peoples Involvement Corporation, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Health Care Association Special Recognition Award Charlene Drew Jarvis Council Member Ward 4: For Achieving both Recognition and the Appreciation by the Members of the DC Health Care Association, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Public Service Award Council Member Charlene Drew Jarvis Beta Zeta Chapter Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Incorporated, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis for Special Inspiration and Service for Roosevelt High School Science Students Award, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Educational Organization for United Latin Americans/ Spanish Senior Center: Presented to Charlene Drew Jarvis in Recognition of Your Support of the Educational Organization for United Latin Americans and the Hispanic Community Award, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Charles Drew Health Center: 4th Annual Board of Directors Special Recognition Award Presented to Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Public Service Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Greater Washington Urban League Inc. Whitney M. Young Jr. Community Service Award for Excellent Service to Education Presented to Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - America's Millennium/ William J. Clinton 2000 - William McKinley 1900 - John Adams - 1800 Award (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Gallery Place: The Groundbreaking Award, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Councilmember Thank You Frank Tucker and CACS Award, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Make Your Mark Beam Signing Ceremony: Washington Convention Center Award, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Washington Convention Center Authority (Washington, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis: The Buck Stops Here! Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Honorable Charlene Drew Jarvis in Recognition of Your Outstanding Commitment and Support - District of Columbia Industrial Revenue Bond Award, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The Victor Building: Construction Commencement Celebration Award, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Housing Finance Agency Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Gold plated 3 leaf clover paperweight with the "May the Road Rise Up to Meet You" Irish Blessing Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The National Theatre 150th Anniversary - 1835-1985 Award (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Courtyard by Marriott Convention Center Washington D.C. Award, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - NABW Capital Group 10-22-87 Award, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Fred Fiske Show - Sterling Tucker Cassette Tape, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis Ward Four Cassette Tape, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Monolog: Silk Shadows Cassette Tape, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Jarvis 2000 Cassette Tape (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jarvis 96- English Cassette Tape, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - McGinty 1-3-97 Cassette Tape, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Washington Planning and Housing Association Crosstrek WDCU-FM Cassette Tape, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "New Election Press Conference Cassette Tape, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Drum-Insight Part 2 Cassette Tape, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Politics Cassette Tape, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "From Whence We Came" Cassette Tape, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Jarvis in '88 Ward 4 DC Cassette Tape, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Interview Cassette Tape, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Jarvis in '88 Ward 4 DC Cassette Tape, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Jarvis in '88 Ward 4 DC Cassette Tape, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Jarvis in '88 Ward 4 DC Cassette Tape, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Mixtape Cassette Tape, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - News Report Cassette Tape, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Council Meeting Minutes Cassette Tape, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Interview Practice Cassette Tape, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Audio Tape, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Affordable Housing Solutions: How Can I Afford to Buy a House? Side 1 Audio Tape, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Affordable Housing Solutions: How Can I Afford to Buy a House? End Panel I - How Can I find a Decent and Affordable Apartment? Panel II Audio Tape, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - #28, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)